<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on GrepKeys</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on GrepKeys</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><atom:link href="https://grepkeys.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hello and welcome to GrepKeys. This website has been set up to help inform you about keyboards in an effort to assist you with buying your first keyboard. Each keyboard page contains a description of the features of the keyboard, the available switches, a sound test and a link to the place we recommend purchasing the keyboard.
So, after all this blurb, it might be time to introduce ourselves. twdly is a newly-forged mechanical keyboard enthusiast, having recently purchased his first board.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/contact/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s two of us that wrote this website: twdly and arzg. Those links will bring you to our respective GitHub profiles. Or, if you&amp;rsquo;re interested, you can read more about us and GrepKeys.</description></item><item><title>Anne Pro 2</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/anne-pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/anne-pro/</guid><description>One the most popular prebuilt keyboards currently Wireless Only available with 60% sizes The Anne Pro 2 is a keyboard by Obinslab that has quickly grown to become one of the most popular keyboards for enthusiasts that haven&amp;rsquo;t yet built their own custom keyboard and is rivalling the Ducky One 2 Mini in popularity due to them both filling a similar niche.
Both these keyboards are 60% keyboards but still maintain everyone function a keyboard is required to fulfil.</description></item><item><title>Apple Wireless Keyboard</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/applewirelesskeyboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/applewirelesskeyboard/</guid><description>Membrane switch results in mediocre typing experience Size, weight and lack of cables results in great portability Only available refurbished or second hand Git gud and buy a real keyboard. Seriously though, it&amp;rsquo;s not very good. The Apple Wireless Keyboard is a keyboard produced by Apple that ships with their desktop computers, but can also be bought separately. At least, it used to be. After many years, Apple decided that they wanted to update their keyboard offering, so they created the Magic Keyboard.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Black</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-black/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-black/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Black is a heavier version of the Cherry MX Red. The only difference between the two switches is the actuation force, with the original Red switches having an actuation force of forty-five grams, but with the Black switches have an actuation force of sixty grams. Similar to the Cherry MX Green, the heavier weight of the Black switch has resulted in it being favoured for typing over gaming.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Blue</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-blue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-blue/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Blue switch is a switch from Cherry known for its extremely loud clickiness, and pronounced tactility. It has an operating force of fifty grams, which is little compared to heavier switch versions such as the Cherry MX Green, but still more than the forty-five grams of the Cherry MX Red. Blues have an actuation point of 2.2 millimetres, again more than the Reds. The tactile bump is significantly more noticeable than the Browns&amp;rsquo; ones.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Brown</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-brown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-brown/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Brown is a very popular switch due to it being a comfortable middle ground between the Cherry MX Red and the Cherry MX Blue. It has the quietness of the Red switch with a slight tactile bump from the Blue switch. This switch has an actuation point of two millimetres, and an operating force of forty-five grams.
However, the Brown switch has created an argument as to whether the Brown switch is a tactile switch as advertised, or a linear switch due to the bump being so subtle.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Clear</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-clear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-clear/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Clear is very similar to the Cherry MX Brown in the way that it has a slight bump but it is slightly heavier. The clear switches require a force of sixty-five grams to actuate while brown switches require forty-five grams to actuate. The clears are most frequently used as a spacebar on keyboards with brown switches.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Green</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-green/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-green/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Green is a switch that is very similar to the Cherry MX Blue. The Green switch inherits the clickiness and tactility of the Blues, but with one major difference; it is slightly heavier. With weight, of course, we mean the force you need to apply to the switch for it to reach the actuation point. To be precise, the Green switch requires eighty grams to actuate, in contrast to the Blues&amp;rsquo; fifty grams &amp;ndash; quite the difference.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Red</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-red/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-red/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Red is a linear switch manufactured by the popular mechanical switch brand Cherry. These switches are generally regarded as one of the best switches for gaming due to their linearity. Linear means that the switch lacks any kind of tactile bump or click at all. Linearity, however, removes any feedback to whether a keystroke has registered, save bottoming out. This can make for a bit of a learning curve for new users.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Silent Red</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-silentred/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-silentred/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Silent Red is a switch that was developed by Cherry with the help from Corsair; a popular &amp;lsquo;gaming&amp;rsquo; keyboard brand. The silent reds were designed to feel and function identically to the Cherry MX Reds but quiter. The reason for developing this switch instead of just using O-rings (small rubber bands placed onto the bottom of a keycap to dampen sound) was that the O-rings would possibly block the RGB lights.</description></item><item><title>Cherry MX Speed</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/cherry-speed/</guid><description>The Cherry MX Speed is a switch that was designed with gaming in the mind. The theory behind it is that a shorter actuation distance means there is less time between attempting to press a key and the keystroke registering. The result is a linear switch similar to the MX Red, but with a mere 1.2 millimetre actuation distance. The 0.8 millimetre difference between the Speeds and some other switches, such as Browns and Reds, may not seem like much.</description></item><item><title>Corsair K95 RGB Platinum</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/corsair-k95/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/corsair-k95/</guid><description>Very expensive for what you get Over the top RGB lighting Requires Corsair&amp;rsquo;s software that currently only supports Windows The Corsair K95 RGB Platinum is a keyboard produced by the popular PC hardware brand Corsair. It was designed to be a no compromises board containing as many features as Corsair could pack into the board. The features this board contains are a detachable wrist rest with reversible rubber to change the texture, six extra keys dedicated to macros, many media keys including a volume scroll, onboard profile storage with buttons to switch between profiles, USB passthrough, n-key rollover and RGB lights with Corsair iCUE support.</description></item><item><title>Ducky One 2 Series</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-one-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-one-2/</guid><description>Great build quality Large variety of styles and switches 60%, 80% and 100% sizes The Ducky One 2 Series is a series of keyboards from the popular brand Ducky. Ducky are well known for the great build quality of all their boards, an expectation that the Ducky One 2 series definitely lives up to. An example of this quality is the set of PBT Doubleshot keycaps that is standard amongst all boards in the series, as well as the frankly ridiculous range of Cherry MX switches they are available with (which is shown above).</description></item><item><title>Ducky Shine 7</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-shine-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-shine-7/</guid><description>Exceptional build quality Expensive but better than everything else in the price range Only available with 100% size The Ducky Shine 7 is Ducky&amp;rsquo;s top tier keyboard and is one of the best boards you can get without custom building a keyboard by yourself. This keyboard is currently only available as a 100% keyboard and has the exact same layout as the full size Ducky One 2 with three volume keys and a calculator key above the number pad.</description></item><item><title>Gateron Blue</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/gateron-blue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/gateron-blue/</guid><description>The Gateron Blue is essentially just a clone of Cherry MX Blues. For this switch, Gateron took Cherry&amp;rsquo;s design, improved it and made it cheaper. Just like the MX Blue, this switch has a loud, tactical bump and a similar actuation force. Many people who have used this switch have decided that the Gateron Blue, despite being a clone, feels better than the MX Blue. This is because the Gateron Blue feels much smoother to press due to the way Gateron molds their sliders.</description></item><item><title>Gateron Brown</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/gateron-brown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/gateron-brown/</guid><description>The Gateron Brown is just a clone of Cherry MX Browns but with a different spring. The change of spring results in a lighter actuation force but mechanical keyboard enthusiasts have noted that the springs make an irritating squeaking noise.
The Gateron Brown, similar to the MX Brown has a tiny bump that isn&amp;rsquo;t quite tactile (sometimes described as a grain of sand being stuck inside the switch) but a slightly lessened actuation force of 45g.</description></item><item><title>Gateron Red</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/gateron-red/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/gateron-red/</guid><description>The Gateron Red is just a clone of the Cherry MX Red but is considered slightly better due to the smoothness of the switch. As explained in the article for the Gateron Blue, the switch is smoother due to Gateron&amp;rsquo;s molding process when making the slider results in smoother plastic and less scratchiness when compared to Cherry&amp;rsquo;s switches.
Just like the MX Red, this switch is linear and requires 45g of force to actuate with an actuation point of 2 millimeters.</description></item><item><title>Kailh Box Black</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-black/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-black/</guid><description>The Kailh Box Black is a clone of the Cherry MX Black with a different style of stem similar to the newer versions of Razer switches. This stem was designed to make the switch more durable to dust and moisture. The Box Black&amp;rsquo;s only difference to the MX Black is a slightly shortened actuation distance of 1.8 millimetres compared to the MX Black&amp;rsquo;s 2 millimetre actuation point.</description></item><item><title>Kailh Box Brown</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-brown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-brown/</guid><description>The Kailh Box Brown is a clone of Cherry MX Brown with a different style of stem similar to the newer versions of Razer switches. This stem was designed to make the switch more durable to dust and moisture. This switch is slightly lighter than MX Browns with a weight of 50g compared the the MX Brown&amp;rsquo;s 55g. It has a slightly shorter actuation distance of 1.8mm compared to the MX Brown&amp;rsquo;s 2mm.</description></item><item><title>Kailh Box Red</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-red/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-red/</guid><description>The Kailh Box Red is a clone of the Cherry MX Red with a different style of stem similar to the newer versions of Razer switches. This stem was designed to make the switch more durable to dust and moisture. The Box Red&amp;rsquo;s only difference to the MX Red is a slightly shortened actuation distance of 1.8 millimetres compared to the MX Red&amp;rsquo;s 2 millimetre actuation point.</description></item><item><title>Kailh Box White</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-white/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/box-white/</guid><description>The Kailh Box White is a clone of the Cherry MX Blue with a different style of stem similar to the newer versions of Razer switches. This stem was designed to make the switch more durable to dust and moisture. The Box White&amp;rsquo;s only difference to the MX Blue is a slightly shortened actuation distance of 1.8 millimetres compared to the MX Blue&amp;rsquo;s 2.2 millimetre actuation point.</description></item><item><title>Membrane Switch</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/membrane/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/membrane/</guid><description>The membrane switch is simultaneously both the most and least popular switch of all. The membrane switch is known for being dirt cheap for manufacturers due to having a single membrane spread over the entire board. This cheapness from not needing a switch for every key has resulted in this switch being used in the vast majority of keyboards. If you buy a keyboard that doesn&amp;rsquo;t advertise a specific switch nor say it is mechanical, you almost definitely have just found a membrane keyboard.</description></item><item><title>Razer Blackwidow Elite</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-blackwidow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-blackwidow/</guid><description>Somewhat overpriced Great media control buttons Razer&amp;rsquo;s software required The Razer Blackwidow Elite is the latest installment in Razer&amp;rsquo;s series of Blackwidow keyboards. The Blackwidow has always been Razer&amp;rsquo;s main keyboard and has been through many iterations since its initial release in 2010. Between 2010 and now, many features have been added such as Razer Synapse™ support, Razer&amp;rsquo;s own switches, RGB lighting, media keys and a removeable wrist rest.</description></item><item><title>Razer Green</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-green/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-green/</guid><description>The Razer Green is a switch that was designed by Razer and is exclusive to their own boards. The Razer Green switch is essentially just a slightly worse Cherry MX Blue. This switch keeps the distinct clicky noise of the MX Blue but loses the tactility. People who have used this switch report the bump as feeling like the Cherry MX Brown&amp;rsquo;s bump.
Razer originally used MX Blues in all their boards until they deigned the Razer Greens.</description></item><item><title>Razer Huntsman Elite</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-huntsman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-huntsman/</guid><description>One of the few ways to get Razer Purple switches Great media keys Very overpriced The Razer Huntsman Elite is Razer&amp;rsquo;s current top keyboard in terms of both functionality and price. Out of all of Razer&amp;rsquo;s keyboards, this is the one with the most features such as a detachable wrist rest, RGB lights with many effects and ways to get more, keycaps that don&amp;rsquo;t use a disgusting font, a gaming mode that disables the windows key and a programmable scroll wheel.</description></item><item><title>Razer Opto-mechanical</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-purple/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-purple/</guid><description>The Razer Opto-mechanical switch (also known as the Razer Purple due to its purple stem) is the newest switch designed by Razer and is also one of the first switches to use a laser as the actuation mechanism. When the switch is idle, a laser is blocked by a part of the slider just above the spring. When the switch is pressed down, the part blocking the laser is also moved down allowing the laser to shine into a sensor that then registers the keystroke.</description></item><item><title>Razer Orange</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-orange/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-orange/</guid><description>The Razer Orange is Razer&amp;rsquo;s attempt at making a replacement for the Cherry MX Brown. It shares many characteristics with the MX Brown such as a subtle bump, two millimetre actuation distance and an actuation force of forty grams.
Just like Razer&amp;rsquo;s other switches, there have been concerns over their claims of an 80 million keystroke durability; especially for older iterations of Razer&amp;rsquo;s switches. Many people have claimed their Razer switches have died long before 80 million keystrokes and, just as explained in the article for the Razer Yellow the Cherry switches may actually be more durable than Razer&amp;rsquo;s switches despite their claims.</description></item><item><title>Razer Yellow</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-yellow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/razer-yellow/</guid><description>The Razer Yellow is Razer&amp;rsquo;s newest mechanical switch. It was designed almost identically to the Cherry MX Speed but can only be found inside Razer&amp;rsquo;s own keyboards. Just like the MX Speed, this switch is linear, has an actuation distance of 1.2 millimetres and an actuation force of forty-five grams. This results in the switch having the same problem as the MX Speed being the low actuation point causing accidental keystrokes.</description></item><item><title>Zealios V2</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/zealios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/switches/zealios/</guid><description>The Zealios V2 is a switch designed by ZealPC and manufactured by Gateron as a response to the insanely popular Holy Panda. The Holy Panda is known for being the most tactile switch that is available today. A combination of its tactility and it only being available during a group buy that occurs just a couple of times a year (maybe even less) the resell price has raised to about $6 for a single switch.</description></item></channel></rss>