<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keyboards on GrepKeys</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/</link><description>Recent content in Keyboards on GrepKeys</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><atom:link href="https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anne Pro 2</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/anne-pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/anne-pro/</guid><description>One the most popular prebuilt keyboards currently Wireless Only available with 60% sizes The Anne Pro 2 is a keyboard by Obinslab that has quickly grown to become one of the most popular keyboards for enthusiasts that haven&amp;rsquo;t yet built their own custom keyboard and is rivalling the Ducky One 2 Mini in popularity due to them both filling a similar niche.
Both these keyboards are 60% keyboards but still maintain everyone function a keyboard is required to fulfil.</description></item><item><title>Apple Wireless Keyboard</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/applewirelesskeyboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/applewirelesskeyboard/</guid><description>Membrane switch results in mediocre typing experience Size, weight and lack of cables results in great portability Only available refurbished or second hand Git gud and buy a real keyboard. Seriously though, it&amp;rsquo;s not very good. The Apple Wireless Keyboard is a keyboard produced by Apple that ships with their desktop computers, but can also be bought separately. At least, it used to be. After many years, Apple decided that they wanted to update their keyboard offering, so they created the Magic Keyboard.</description></item><item><title>Corsair K95 RGB Platinum</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/corsair-k95/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/corsair-k95/</guid><description>Very expensive for what you get Over the top RGB lighting Requires Corsair&amp;rsquo;s software that currently only supports Windows The Corsair K95 RGB Platinum is a keyboard produced by the popular PC hardware brand Corsair. It was designed to be a no compromises board containing as many features as Corsair could pack into the board. The features this board contains are a detachable wrist rest with reversible rubber to change the texture, six extra keys dedicated to macros, many media keys including a volume scroll, onboard profile storage with buttons to switch between profiles, USB passthrough, n-key rollover and RGB lights with Corsair iCUE support.</description></item><item><title>Ducky One 2 Series</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-one-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-one-2/</guid><description>Great build quality Large variety of styles and switches 60%, 80% and 100% sizes The Ducky One 2 Series is a series of keyboards from the popular brand Ducky. Ducky are well known for the great build quality of all their boards, an expectation that the Ducky One 2 series definitely lives up to. An example of this quality is the set of PBT Doubleshot keycaps that is standard amongst all boards in the series, as well as the frankly ridiculous range of Cherry MX switches they are available with (which is shown above).</description></item><item><title>Ducky Shine 7</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-shine-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/ducky-shine-7/</guid><description>Exceptional build quality Expensive but better than everything else in the price range Only available with 100% size The Ducky Shine 7 is Ducky&amp;rsquo;s top tier keyboard and is one of the best boards you can get without custom building a keyboard by yourself. This keyboard is currently only available as a 100% keyboard and has the exact same layout as the full size Ducky One 2 with three volume keys and a calculator key above the number pad.</description></item><item><title>Razer Blackwidow Elite</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-blackwidow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-blackwidow/</guid><description>Somewhat overpriced Great media control buttons Razer&amp;rsquo;s software required The Razer Blackwidow Elite is the latest installment in Razer&amp;rsquo;s series of Blackwidow keyboards. The Blackwidow has always been Razer&amp;rsquo;s main keyboard and has been through many iterations since its initial release in 2010. Between 2010 and now, many features have been added such as Razer Synapse™ support, Razer&amp;rsquo;s own switches, RGB lighting, media keys and a removeable wrist rest.</description></item><item><title>Razer Huntsman Elite</title><link>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-huntsman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://grepkeys.github.io/keyboards/razer-huntsman/</guid><description>One of the few ways to get Razer Purple switches Great media keys Very overpriced The Razer Huntsman Elite is Razer&amp;rsquo;s current top keyboard in terms of both functionality and price. Out of all of Razer&amp;rsquo;s keyboards, this is the one with the most features such as a detachable wrist rest, RGB lights with many effects and ways to get more, keycaps that don&amp;rsquo;t use a disgusting font, a gaming mode that disables the windows key and a programmable scroll wheel.</description></item></channel></rss>